Matthew S. Robertson

matthewebdev@gmail.com

Summary

I am currently working full-time in the field of mental health but have years of experience working with technology. I am aiming to shift careers into the IT field. I have a wealth of knowledge in the field ranging from electronic repair to web development.

Work Experience

DAYMARK RECOVERY SERVICES / LEXINGTON, NC / HUMAN SERVICE COUNSELOR / JULY 2013 - PRESENT

- Work with child and adolescent populations with behavioral disorders
- Planned and scheduled daily activities and lessons
- Assisted in set up and design of programs

- Hired on as an associate professional and prompted to qualified professional after two years of experience
- Maintained computer and electronic equipment

CPR CELL PHONE REPAIR / HIGH POINT, NC / LEAD TECHNICIAN / NOVEMBER 2011 - PRESENT

- Hired on as a full-time technician and was promoted to lead technician within three months
- Promoted to store manager one year later but stepped down to lead technician after gaining second employment and moving to part-time
- Responsible for training new technicians and discovering new best practices
- Repaired a wide array of electronics from cell phones to personal computers

SPRINT / WINSTON SALEM, NC / TECHNICAL CONSULTANT / MARCH 2009 - NOVEMBER 2013

- Troubleshoot and repair cellular devices with network and hardware problems
- Customer retention

Maintained account services

BEST BUY / WINSTON SALEM, NC / SALES CONSULTANT / JUNE 2007 - MARCH 2009

- Sold personal computers and hardware
- Received several awards for highest sales

• Responsible for daily quota of computer service sales

Education

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN PSYCHOLOGY / GREENSBORO, NC / MAY 2012

University of North Carolina at Greensboro

ASSOCIATE OF ARTS IN PSYCHOLOGY / THOMASVILLE, NC / DECEMBER 2009

Davidson County Community College

Technical Skills

- Proficient in Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, etc)
- Proficient in multiple operating systems (Windows, Mac OSX)
- Experience working with several programming languages and frameworks(HTML, CSS, JavaScript, etc)
- Proficient troubleshooting and diagnosing issues with electronic hardware and software
- Proficient in repairing small electronics including soldering onboard components
- Experience with design and developing websites and web apps